worksafebc.com 2013-09-22

# WorkSafeBC.com - Privacy

## Privacy policy

The Workers' Compensation Board of B.C.(WorkSafeBC) recognizes the privacy concerns of visitors to our web site and the importance of protecting the privacy of any personal information collected about our visitors. As a general policy, we do not automatically collect any personal information (such as name, address, or e-mail address) from visitors to our site. The type of information that we may collect is non-personal information used to optimize our web pages for your computer (for example, the identity of your Internet browser, the type of operating system you use, and the domain name of your Internet service provider). We may also use non-personal information to determine the total number of visitors to our web site.

####  Personal information

We only collect personal information about visitors to our site when visitors knowingly and voluntarily submit the information. Whenever we do collect such information, the following applies: 

  1. We will notify you when we are collecting personal information, and will let you know the intended use of the information.
  2. We will only use personal information for the purposes that were disclosed at the time of collection as the purpose for the collection, or for uses consistent with those purposes. 
  3. We will not transfer personal information to third parties, except as required or authorized under the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act ("FIPP Act"). 
  4. We may use the collected information to respond to your specific requests. We may also use it in aggregate form without personal identifiers to make our site better and more responsive to our visitors' needs. This statistical compilation of non-identifiable information may be used by the Workers' Compensation Board of B.C. or be provided to others for the Board's marketing, advertising, or research purposes. The Workers' Compensation Board of B.C. complies with privacy laws by maintaining safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of such information.

Please be advised that any and all information entered, including personal information, may be collected and used in determining eligibility for registration and classification.

####  Use of cookies 

Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make it easier for you to use a web site by saving passwords, purchases, and preferences while you visit the site. The Workers' Compensation Board of B.C. does not use cookies to retrieve information other than the information that was originally sent in a cookie. Most browsers accept cookies automatically. You can set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when they are being sent.

####  Links to other sites 

This site may be linked to other web sites within our organization, or to web sites operated by others. The Workers' Compensation Board of B.C. is not responsible for the content or practices of third-party web sites that may be linked to or from this site.   

#### Privacy policy changes

The Workers' Compensation Board of B.C. reviews its privacy policy periodically, and it may be subject to change.
